<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on</title><link>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/</link><description>Recent content in Home on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Remote API</title><link>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/api/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a websocket based API for communicating with the remote, running on port 946(YIO). Mainly used by the web configurator tool and the YIO Dock.
The API automatically starts on power up and is always running in the background. The API is stopped, before wifi is turned off and started, after wifi is turned on.
Messages are sent in JSON format.
Remote Authentication When a client connects, the remote sends a JSON message:</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/faq/</guid><description>Can I update the Dock Firmware manually? Yes, you need to compile or download a new dock firmware image. Then use curl to push the firmware to the dock with the following command:
curl -F &amp;quot;file=@firmware.bin&amp;quot; http://&amp;lt;Dock IP&amp;gt;/update You can also use ESPHome-Flasher to update the firmware via USB.
How can I change the timezone or set the time manually? remote-os v2 The default system timezone is set to UTC.</description></item><item><title>Supporters</title><link>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/supporters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetimewalker.github.io/documentation/docs/home/supporters/</guid><description>Big thanks to the following supporters who pledged on Kickstarter to support the project!
Gabor Balint Ian benjinho Maximilian Franzke Anakyn Labs intelliweights Vito Telischak Victor Rasmussen The Creative Fund by BackerKit If you like the project, consider donating :) Buy us a coffee</description></item></channel></rss>